巴兰基亚  哥伦比亚
机  械  师
新奥尔良  路易斯安那州
这份工作需要一种信念
What I do requires a certain mindset.
我负责完成任务
I do assignments.
消灭指定目标
Designated targets.
其中一些得伪造成意外
Some jobs need to look like accidents.
跳跃点
驳船经过路线和方向
其它一些则必须嫁祸他人
Others must cost suspicion on someone else.
我从中筛选出有用的信息
I select few need to select a clear message.
扣动扳机是很容易
Pulling a trigger is easy.
但最好的结果是
The best jobs are the one's nobody
根本没人意识到你的存在
ever knows you were there.
哥伦比亚毒枭 佐治 拉尔 意外溺水而亡
湖中仙女昨晚来找我
Lake of fairy pay me a visit last night.
给了我一大瓶陈酿苏格兰威士忌
Left me a big old bottle of scotch.
把他整得飘飘然
He went sprung for this scotch.
回见 亨利
See ya, Henry.
我怎么会答应你来这种鬼地方?
Why the fuck do I let you drag me into this shithole?
别抱怨了 哈里
You're a snob, Harry.
这每天这么多人进进出出
1,100 people come through here everyday.
谁会记得我们两个人来过
Aren't you remember two fellas passing through?
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧 也许会有人记得他俩
Of course, people might remember them.
我以后的日子就想搞清楚一点
All I got in the future purpose on
我是不是没了他们就活不了了
if I could go anywhere without them nowhere.
那让他们穿合身点的西装
Try to get them suits to fit
不然看起来太搞笑了
they look like cartoons.
一切都顺利吗?
Everything went okay?
搞定了
It got done.
你也知道 我比你强
You know, I'm better than you, you know.
所以他们给你派那些任务
That's why they give you those job.
他们不会考虑交给我 因为...
They can't give a little to Harry because...
如果交给我 还得让你去善后...
If they were get to Harry, then you would take care of it...
他们只关心这些
and that's all they care about.
一步到位 不留烂摊子
Services, rendered, no loose ends.
这我无法改变
Fait accompli.
你就是台杀人机器
You're a goddamn machine.
你很有洞察力 如果你这样的人...
You see things. If you people ...
和我不同 和其他人都不同
Differently than I do differently
那你就有个问题 亚瑟
than anybody does. But you got a problem, Arthur.
-你需要个同伴 -我有你 哈里
- You do need companionship. - I have you, Harry.
那你比我想得还要糟
Then, you are in deeper shit than I thought.
斯蒂文怎么样?
So, how's Steven?
我有说过 我给他在私人保安公司找了份工作吗?
Did I tell you I got him a job at a private security firm?
他上个月被人炒了
They kicked him out last month.
他把人家打得半死
He hit some guy half to death.
该死的 太失望了
Goddamn disappointment.
以前是这样 现在也是这样
It always has been. It always will be.
给他打个电话
Call him.
我打给他? 为什么?
Me, call him? For what?
他也许需要你的鼓励
He probably needs to hear from you.
走吧 我给你拿钱去
Let's go. I got your money.
来 和我跳舞吧
Come on. Dance with me.
来嘛 求你了
Come on, please.
你饿了吗?
Are you hungry?
当然
Sure.
-我得走了 -好吧
- I gotta go. - Okay.
你都不告诉我你叫什么吗?
You ever gonna tell me your name?
亚瑟
Arthur.
少唬人了
Nice try.
你可不叫亚瑟
But you are not Arthur.
感觉你更可能叫...戴维
No. More like a... David.
或是布拉德
Or Brad.
好吧 回见 布拉德
Yeah. See you Brad.
需要机械师
哈里 M. 麦肯纳
环球工程公司
Global Engineering.
我打来是为了广告的事
I'm calling about the ad.
一定是搞错了
There must be a mistake.
请稍等一下
One moment, please.
广告内容已证实 信息准确无误
The advertisement was proved. The information is accurate.
我要一个会面
I want a meeting.
回头联系你
We get back to you.
毕肖普先生 迪恩先生同意与你会面
Mr. Bishop, Mr. Dean has agree to a meeting.
一架私人专机会在一小时后
Private jet will pick you up in one
载你前往他选定的中立区
hour to leave you to a neutral side of his choosing.
你有十五分钟时间
You've been allowed fifteen minutes.
之后专机会送你回去
The jet will then return you.
我们告诉你要10点回家
When we tell you to be home at 10 o'clock,
就是10点 而不是11点半
we mean 10, not 11.30.
我不管 宝贝儿 你妈妈被你吓坏了
I don't care, baby. You scared
我罚你禁足两个星期
your mother to death. You're grounded for two weeks.
稍等
Just one second.
那我管不着
That's not my problem.
好吧 听着 禁足十天
All right, look. Ten days and
加上两个周六到收容所做义工
you'll volunteer two Saturdays at the shelter.
减到八天的话就得去三个周六
Eight days and three Saturdays.
-戒指很靓 -就这么定了
- Nice ring. - Done.
-我也想要一个 -不可能
- I wanna get one of those. - You can't.
世界冠军才有
Unless you were a world champion.
那就告诉我 我来处理
Just tell me and I come and fix it.
好了 来吧
All right. Let's go.
我刚在和个十六岁小孩谈判
I just been out negotiate by a sixteen years old.
我们边走边聊吧
Let's take a walk.
六个月前 我们接到一份委托
Six months ago, we were commission to
你从没接到过这么大的委托
under take the largest contract you ever to attempted.
这次的目标比我们
The target was far more high
以往的目标要难搞得多
profile than we are normally comfortable with.
我们差点放弃这次任务
The job was to reach a pass up.
目标是在南非吗?
The target was South African?
目标逃到了南非
The target fled to South Africa.
我们就在开普敦展开行动
There's where we made our move in Cape Town.
用了六个月时间准备
Take six months to set up.
我派了一个五人小组
I assign the team of five
每个人对任务的了解都很有限
operatives to work in a constrain on the mission.
五个人都死了 有个知道内情的人杀了他们
All five were killed. Someone knew everything.
组里也许有你认识的人
You probably knew someone from that team.
我认识他 塞巴斯蒂安
I knew this one. Sebastian.
你知道公司的程序 毕肖普先生
You know how this company works, Mr. Bishop.
只有两个合伙人知道任务信息
Only two partners know the details of any given job.
而这两个人 就是我和哈里 麦肯纳
Two people knew the details here. Me and Harry McKenna.
哈里出卖了我们
Harry sold us out.
我们查了他的财政情况
We pulled his financials.
这是他最近的海外存款
Take a look at recent offshore deposits.
有一笔两星期前
There's one there on two weeks ago
转入的款子 两千万美元
twenty million US dollars.
他年纪渐长 弱点也慢慢暴露
He's gotten old. He's gotten weak.
他债务累累 离婚了
He's loaded with debts, his divorce,
还有个不省心的儿子
his cause and troubled son.
这都使他变得软弱
They made him vulnerable.
过去的十三年来
And for the past 13 years,
我都完全效忠于他
I have been fiercely loyal to him.
我是最尊敬他的人
There is no one I respected more.
但现在哈里 麦肯纳已成了害群之马
But Harry McKenna has poisoned the well.
必须把他除掉
He needs to be removed.
刻不容缓
Immediately.
让我和他谈谈
Let me talk to him.
听着 我知道你们的交情很深
Look. I appreciate your connection with Harry,
但这事儿没有商量的余地
but there is no turning back, here.
是他跨过了界限
He has cross his rubicon.
只要他还活着 公司就有危险
Everyday that he's alive, puts this company in danger.
而我们都希望你来处理此事
Now that we all prefer that you handle this ...
考虑到你们之间的关系
Giving your relationship, you're in
你是小心谨慎和干净利落的最佳人选
best position to get this done quickly and discreetly.
老实说
And to be honest with you,
我也不想让哈里死得很痛苦
I hate the idea of Harry suffer unnecessarily.
我们不想找外人
We don't wanna go on the outside source.
除非是情况所迫
But we will if we have to.
失陪一下
Excuse me a second.
杰西 谈判结束了 抱歉
Jess, negotiations are closed, I'm sorry.
我在开会 稍等
I'm in a meeting. Hang on a second.
给你48小时 不然我们就另想法子
48 hours or we'll proceed the options.
肌肉男 不管你听到了什么
Hey, square. Whatever the expression,
都假装没听到
quit what you have heard.
我是说 罗斯福真是我的英雄
I mean, Roosevelt was truly my hero.
他居然能习惯这该死的轮椅
I mean the way he dealt with this. Damn chair.
把你的裤子提一下 好吗?
Please, pull your trouser up. Would you?
拜托 把裤子提一下
Please, pull your trouser up.
这西装的确不太衬你们
Those suits doesn't really fit you guys very well.
暗杀行动被泄露 五名嫌疑人被枪杀
喂
Yeah?
快离开那栋大楼 哈里
Get out of the building, Harry.
怎么了 亚瑟?
Arthur?
今晚他们要来杀你
They coming for you tonight.
-谁要来? -迪恩
- Who, who is coming? - Dean.
带上能用的防身武器快离开
Take whatever you can use against them and get out.
天啊...
Ohh jesus...
-你有剪刀吗? -有
- Do you have a pair of scissors? - Yes.
到电梯大厅去
Go to the elevator lobby.
这就去
On my way.
看来第十八层断电了
Looks like we got a power out on the 18th floor.
在备用电源启动之前
You have 15 seconds to get to the
你有十五秒时间去服务电梯那
service elevator before the emergency power comes on.
有手动开关吗?
Is there a clip here?
输入大楼编号
Punching the building number.
我们不是断了电吗?
I thought we cut the power off?
服务电梯有另一套独立密码
Service elevator had the work on a separate password.
我进去了
I'm in.
到地下室去
Press the basement floor.
需要十八秒
The elevator will take 18 seconds to get there.
那层楼是空置的
The level is empty and unused.
走下坡道
Take the ramp.
有扇门能通向隔壁大楼
Connects to the building next door.
能通往地下车库
Leads to an underground parking lot.
见鬼
Shit.
这幢楼还没有监控摄像头
The security cameras haven't be
所以他们看不到你
fitted in this building yet. So, they will be blind.
好 现在你该到地下车库了
Okay, you should be entering the parking lot.
我的车在这
My van is here.
我停在这的
I left it there.
见鬼
Oh, shit.
你让我避开了自己的保安
You get me to circumvent my own security.
没人发觉我离开
Nobody sees me leave.
这是为了什么? 开普敦吧?
So, what's this? Cape Town right?
果然
Right.
这次是什么借口?
So, what's the story here?
汽车抢劫吗?
Car jacking?
让警察在这座城市的
Police will find my van
某个阴暗角落发现我的车...
somewhere in shithole section of the city...
被拆得一点不剩吗?
Stripped and up on blocks?
差不多吧
Something like that.
很有想象力
It's like, editorial a vision.
我没看错你
You're my idea.
[拉丁语]
Amat Victoria Curam
胜利垂青有准备的人
Victory Loves Preparation
好吧 我开了几枪 算是反抗过了...
Yeah, I get off a couple of shots, there is struggle...
他们抢了我的枪 生活就是这样
They get my gun. c'est la vie.
起码我还爷们地反抗了一把
At least I don't go down looking like a pussy.
这把枪跟了我33年
I have that for 33 years.
第六舰队的比斯利海军上将送我的礼物
Gift from Admiral Beasly, Sixth fleet.
这也是我第一次用这把枪
That is the first time I ever fired it.
你为什么不杀我?
Why didn't you kill me?
杀了你 他们还会派其他人来
They just send somebody else.
我宁愿是你 亚瑟
I would rather it was you, Arthur.
生活就是这样无奈
You have to live with it.
-天煞的亚瑟 毕肖普 -节哀顺变
- Arthur fucking Bishop. - Sorry for your loss.
他对你来说更重要 伙计
More of a loss for you than me, buddy.
好久不见了
It's a long time.
你能顺路送我去我爸家吗?
Hey, would you give me a ride to my father's house?
你父亲经常说起你
Your father, talked about you a lot.
说你们一起的时光 也许是他瞎编的
Talk about spending time with you. Maybe, make it up.
得了吧
Give it a rest, will you.
他总是三句话离不开你
He always bringing you up.
他说他很后悔
He had regrets stay with him.
那他干嘛不给我打电话
And he've could pick up the phone anytime.
我给你看样东西
I want to show you something.
我小时候很喜欢这里
I love this place as a kid.
很令人敬佩吧
It's pretty impressive, huh?
他们所有人都效忠于国家
Everyone of them, serve their country.
我想我还是可以去参军...
I guess I could still, on list...
让他们以我为傲
You know, make them proud.
才怪
I'm fucking with you.
不知道你有没有我爸的照片 那啥...
I don't know if you have a picture of my father? Maybe...
也许你想要一张
You want one.
看来你不准备留下啊?
Looks you're not planning on sticking around?
怎么留 他又没留遗嘱
For what? He didn't leave a will.
账户里没一分钱 银行会把房子收走
The accounts are empty. Banks gonna take the house.
等律师们清算了这的所有权
By the time of the lawyers sitting a stake
这里就他妈渣都不剩了
it through with the rest not gonna be a fucking thing left.
你准备去哪里?
Where you headed?
有几个地方能去
I had some place.
缺钱吗?
Need some money?
不用 谢了
No, thanks.
我找了个人过来看看那辆车值几钱
I got a guy come to the house. He's gonna look at the car.
也许这能让我撑过这一阵
I think that probably get me through on the next spot.
那些枪呢?
What about the guns?
我在想 不如我今晚出去
I was thinking about going out
做掉几个抢劫汽车的混蛋
and killing myself a couple of car jackers tonight.
这么多抢劫汽车的呢 杀得完吗?
Just any all around the males of jack car, huh?
话是这样没错 但谁知道呢
Yeah, you never know I might
也许我走运撞见杀我爸的那几个混球
get lucky find the guys that kill my dad.
那样你会好受些吗?
That'll make you feel better?
我怎么知道
Fuck if I know.
到时就知道了
I'll find out.
振作点 斯蒂夫
Step it up, Steve.
毕肖普...
Hey, Bishop...
究竟是什么样的人渣
What kind of person shoot someone
会朝个坐轮椅的开枪?
in a wheelchair, anyway?
要帮忙吗?
Hey, you need some help?
不 我自己能行
No, I think I got it.
我本来过来找个朋友
I suppose to meet a friend and I
可能我把地址搞错了
might of get the address wrong.
是吧 也许
Yeah, maybe.
也可能是我自己转晕了
But maybe the address got me wrong.
-车很炫 老兄 -谢谢
- Nice car, man. Nice car. - Thanks.
-能给我吗? -啥?
- Can I have it? - What?
我要抢你的车 混球
I'm leaving you of your automobile, motherfucker.
给我滚出来
Out of the car.
-真的吗? -当然
- Seriously? - Seriously.
真他妈见鬼 好吧
Jesus fucking christ. Okay, okay.
抢劫汽车的人渣
Car jacker.
你用这枪打死他的吗?
You shoot him with this?
就是这把枪吗?
Is this the gun you used?
不是吗?
No?
这可不行
Hey, bad move.
下次做事前考虑清楚 斯蒂夫?
Hope you think this through, did you Steve?
虽然看起来不像 但今晚算你走运...
Its may not seem like it but tonight your lucky night...
雷蒙
Raymond.
你就当是自己摔倒了 不然别怪我们不客气
You fell down. we could come looking for you.
滚
Get out of here.
有动机的杀人是最愚蠢的
Stupid to kill someone when you have a motive.
这会让你成为众矢之的
Might as well paint a bulls eye on your back.
-我才不在乎 -我知道
- I don't give a shit. - I'm aware.
快滚回去
Get out of here.
我一直在想那晚你说的话
I was thinking about what were you saying the other night.
把你知道的东西都教给我
And uh...I wanna know what you know.
上网吧 网上都有
Go online. It's all on the Internet.
但我不光想知道 还要动手去做
But, I don't wanna read it. I wanna do it.
-做什么? -毕肖普 别糊弄我了
- Do what exactly? - Bishop, don't bullshit me.
我了解你 还有他的事
I know about you. And him.
他是你的导师 他待你比我亲
He was your mentore. He chose you over me.
你欠他的
You owe him.
现在他死了
Now that he's gone, he
屁都没留给我 所以现在你欠我了
left me with fucking nothing, you owe me now.
回家去吧 斯蒂夫
Go home, Steve.
还待售哦
Still for sale.
我知道你想要这艘船 错过了可要后悔一辈子
I know you want it. No other lifetime for this.
要建议吗? 听从你的直觉
Want some advice? Follow what this tells you.
你的直觉想要告诉你什么
He's try to tell you something.
那就是 你想要开着这艘船去流浪
He's telling you, you homesick for a place you never been.
埃博拉诺街8600号 明早七点见
8600 Elborano Street. 7 A.M tomorrow.
-这是什么地方 -动物收容所
- What is this place? - It's an animal shelter.
我知道这是哪里
Yeah, I know what this is.
-我是说我们来干嘛 -找一条这样的狗
- Why are we here? - I look for a dog like this.
可以的话收养一年
Under a year if possible.
我觉得你更适合养猫
I think you more for a cat person.
你知道机械师的工作是什么吗?
You know what a Mechanic is,
除了那些常识以外?
aside of its obvious definition?
处理事务 解决问题 完成契约
A guy who fix his things, problems, its contracts.
-是个杀手 -我负责完成任务
- A hit man. - I do assignments.
-消灭指定目标 -这我没问题
- Designated targets. - I can do that.
-我见识过 -不 你没有
- I've seen some shit. - No, you haven't.
你根本不了解我 毕肖普
You know shit about me, Bishop.
斯蒂文 杰克逊 麦肯纳
Steven Jackson McKenna.
出生在马里兰州的巴尔的摩
Born in Baltimore, Maryland.
你12岁时母亲去世
Your mother died when you was 12.
从此你对伏特加上了瘾
Makes you're a pain-mate on vodka.
你高中时转过三次学
You attended 3 different high schools
格兰特 帕克和蒙洛
Grunt, The Parc and Munro.
体育很好
Light in four sports,
拿到了迈阿密大学的奖学金...
got a scholarship from Miami ...
后又因贩毒未遂罪
that was rescinded upon a conviction
而被撤销了奖学金
of possession within an attempt to distribute.
还因在马路上殴打两位前女友
And four misdemeanor for aggravated
被指控为行为不当
assault on local treads against two different girlfriends.
因街头斗殴而断过膝盖骨
Broke your kneecap in a street fight.
还不想让别人知道 就自己编了个故事
Didn't wanna tell anyone so you lie a tale on its own.
说是在射靶场出了意外
Only range went over the length.
我还可以给你看X光片
I show the X-rays if you like.
我朋友想收养这个小家伙
A friend there would like to adopt this little fella.
你好丫 狗狗
Hey, boy.
这份工作需要一种信念
What I do requires a certain mindset.
复仇只会蒙蔽了你的眼
Revenge is an emotion that can get you killed.
所以 别再干昨晚那种蠢事了
So, no more stupid stuffs like the other night.
好好照顾它 和它交个好朋友
Walk it, feel it, make it your best friend.
明天十一点 费舍广场见
Tomorrow, eleven, Fisher Square.
带着狗去瑞文戴尔的咖啡店
Take the dog to the coffee shop in Riverdale.
要一杯黑咖啡
Order a coffee. Black.
选靠窗的位子坐下
Sit at the table by the window,
玩报纸上的数独游戏
and do the sudoku puzzle in the paper.
-和狗狗好好玩玩 -要多久?
- Play nice with the dog. - For how long?
一小时
One hour.
接下来的三周每天都得去
Every day, for the next three weeks.
是你干得好事
This is yours.
这些也要熟记
Practice some of this.
保险公司熟知每一种
Insurance companies know everything
致人死亡的方式
about how people die.
他们手下的精算师写了书
They have books with actuaries.
列出了所有能想到的死因
List of every cause of death imaginable.
我看这些玩意有嘛用?
Why did you show to me all of the fuck of this?
良好的判断力来源于经验
Good judgment comes from
而经验则来自失败的教训
experience and all of that comes from bad judgment.
箱子下面是你的床 自己收拾吧
Beds under the boxes. Help yourself.
这车你弄了多久?
How long you've been working on it?
-两年 -很炫
- Two years. - It's nice.
-我们啥时候开出去溜溜 -我们? 没门
- When are we gonna go for a ride? - We? Never.
该进入下一阶段训练了
Time to take your training to the next level.
-他是谁? -一起的
- Who is that? - He's good.
我让你一个人来
I only checked you out.
那我以后再来吧 比傻站这强
I can come back. Rather than stand out here.
你要知道 现在情况变幻莫测
I gotta tell you man. I'm skittish right now.
我不知道现在是否该抛头露面
I'm not sure if this a good time for me to be doing anything.
最近风声有点紧
There a lot of shit wind, you know.
我把清单和钱带来了
I brought the list and the money.
现在有点难办
Now is not the good time.
给我看看清单
Let me see the list.
-什么时候要? -越快越好
- All this been when? - As soon as possible.
好吧 给我一天时间搞定
All right. Take me day to make it happen.
把钱给我吧
Give me out the money.
-窒息式自慰致死 -没错
- Auto Erotic is fixation? - Yup.
我就是觉得你该近距离观摩一次
I just thought you should see one up close.
不许再碰它
Don't ever touch this.
跟我来
Follow me.
-他是谁 -任务 仅此而已
- Who was he? - A job. Nothing more, nothing less.
你非要知道的话 他是个非法军火商
Make you feel better, he was an illegal arms dealer.
他把武器卖给任何人
Sold weapons to anyone.
弑警犯 帮派成员 恐怖分子
Cop killers, gang bangers, terrorists.
他从不区别对待
He didn't discriminate.
给你档案
Here's the file.
是咖啡店那家伙吗?
The guy from the coffee shop?
这次你自己动手
All yours.
他是真人不露相
You wouldn't know by looking at him.
其实他是另一个组织的机械师
But he's a Mechanic for another group.
他唯一的习惯就是
His only routine is
每天早上9点到10点要喝咖啡
coffee every morning from nine to ten.
除了这里 他不会两次出现在同一个地方
He isn't going any place twice, except here.
他受到隔离和保护
He's isolated and protected.
不可能悄悄地接近他
No way in without him seeing it's coming.
但他有两个弱点
Except he has two weaknesses.
-吉娃娃狗 -我可以坐这吗?
- Chihuahuas. - Mind if I sit down?
-请便 -还有男孩
- Please. - And boys.
-年轻男孩 -黑咖啡
- Young boys. - Coffee, black.
尽管他观察了你六个星期
Although he checked you out for the past six weeks
但他没发现你的真实身份
and found no connection to you in his world.
他只觉得你是个有些茫然的小帅哥
All he sees is a good looking kid who's kind of lost.
-我可以抱抱它吗? -好
- Mind if I hold him? - Yeah.
-他就喜欢那样 -来吧 宝贝
- He likes that. - Come here, baby.
如果他对你感兴趣 他首先会问你
If he's interested, first thing he'll do is ask you...
你住在附近吗? 斯蒂夫
Do you live around here, Steve?
-你要回答 -我没有固定地方
- Your answer should be. - Well, I'm bouncing around.
那意味着你生活受挫 需要一些建议
Which means you're broke and open to suggestions.
和我的狗狗一起
With my buddy.
-接着他会问你 -过会想和我喝一杯吗?
- Then asks you if... - You want to get a drink later on with me?
-你要回答 -好啊
- Your answer should be. - Yeah.
太好了 你也觉得很好吧?
Great. That's great ain't it?
-这是镇静剂 -真有趣
- This one is Trazepam. - Groovy.
你是让我杀了他 不是强暴他吧?
You want me to kill him not rape him, right?
两到三滴 他就会神志不清
Two to three drops, he's woozy.
超过六滴 他的大脑就会
Over six, somehow stops
停止工作并在20分钟内死亡
in his brain dead in under than 20 minutes.
在酒吧下手 要干净利落
Do it in the bar. Make it clean.
这些高档场所的酒都兑过水...
All these fancy places there are always watered down it...
所以你才会醉得这么快
So I think that's why you are going down so fast.
-他们一杯都没兑过水 -真不错
- They don't watery down in one. - It's really good.
-还要吗? -好啊
- You want more? - Yeah.
-占美臣酒 是吧 -2盎司 谢谢
- Jameson, right? - Jamesons double, please.
别和那家伙纠缠 在酒吧下手 干净利落
Don't mess around with this guy. Do it in the bar, make it clean.
把你会的都教给我 我也想做
I wanna know what you know. I wanna do it.
怎么了? 有什么好笑?
What? What's funny?
没什么... 我只是觉得喝得太多了
Nothing. No..I just..I think I had to many.
不 接着来
No, come on.
不 我觉得我喝完这杯 然后就...
No..I think I'm gonna finish this one and I'm gonna...
我真要去睡觉了 不过真的很开心
I really should go to bed.. But this is very..It's funny.
斯蒂夫
Steve.
你没事吧?
You all right?
-没事 你呢 -我很好 老弟
- Yeah, how are you? - I'm good, man.
能送送你吗? 我的车就在这里
Hey, can I give you a ride someplace? Car is right here.
走吧 上车 我有东西给你看
Come on. Get in. I want to show you something.
是吗?
Yeah?
他身高6尺7 体重300磅 很有杀伤力
He's six foot seven, 300 pounds and lethal.
别跟他硬碰硬
Do not take this guy up.
无论如何 都不要上他的车
Whatever you do, don't ever get into his car.
你觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
-很漂亮 -我给你倒杯酒
- It's beautiful. - Let me get you a drink.
-你会画画吗? -是啊 只是业余爱好
- Do you paint? - Yeah, It's more of a hobby really.
画得相当不错
Pretty serious hobby.
干杯
Cheers.
那是客厅和壁炉
That's the sitting area and fireplace.
凉爽又轻松的房间
Chillaxing room.
Chillaxing chilling和relaxing的合成词
这是我最引以为傲的地方 就在这
This is the place I most proud of, right here.
-这个不错 -这是14世纪的佛像
- This is good. - That is, 14th-century Buddha.
不过在这个国家被糟蹋了
And that was a bitch to get into this country.
有朋友真好
It's nice to have friends.
有个对你有意义的好朋友
Have a good friends who make a difference.
你有好朋友吗?
Do you got good friends?
我是说 真正的好朋友
I mean, really good friends.
你抖得像片叶子
You're shaking like a leaf.
坐下
Sit down.
好吧 好吧
All right...all right.
慢点 小家伙
Slow down, cowboy.
我说过要干净利落
I tell you to make it clean.
回头见
See you later.
怎么弄的 工作还是寻开心?
Was it work or a pleasure?
真希望有人也能这样对我
I wish someone would hurt me like that.
等等
Hey..
谢谢 我决定叫它亚瑟
Thanks. I'm gonna call him Arthur.
按#1
怎么...
Yeah..
你让一个外人替你完成任务
You use an outside individual to complete your assignment.
这违反了我们的约定
That's a violation of our arrangement.
我只和哈里有约定 我们没什么约定
My arrangement was with Harry. You and I don't have one.
纯粹的利益关系
Just the price.
我觉得我训练他对你会有用
I think someone trained by me would be viable to you.
哈里 麦肯纳的儿子吗?
Harry McKenna's son?
他知道是你杀了他父亲吗?
Is he know you killed his father?
这次任务要速战速决
This job needs to be done immediately.
客户愿意额外加钱
Clients want to pay premium for it.
还是不要了 间隔时间太短
I don't think so. It's too quick.
你的行为让我们大家都感到相当不便
Your behaviour is making me and the others extremely uneasy.
这次任务你会被盯得很紧
You're on a short leash with this one.
先把这个档案看了
The file is a priority.
我会研究一下
I'll look it up.
我是上帝的使者
I am one with God.
上帝赐福于我 而我福泽祂的子民
God touches me and I touch his people.
安德鲁 沃恩 45岁 自称新救世主
Andrew Vaughn, 45 years old. Calls himself the new Messiah.
-沃恩神父 -叫我沃恩就行
- Reverend Vaughn. - Just Vaughn.
我不是神父
I'm not a reverend.
我没有任何宗教在后面支持我
I'm not endorsed by the end of the world religion.
我凌驾于他们之上 我就是沃恩
I'm above them, I am Vaughn.
他通过教堂和修道院
He has made millions of dollars
还有电视节目 捞了上百万美金
to his churches, his ministries, his television program,
总的来说 他就是个邪教头子
basically, he is running a cult.
往心脏注射12CC肾上腺素
Adrenaline shot to the heart, 12CC
他会在3分钟内死亡
and he's dead under three minutes.
肾上腺素靠不住 可能是暂时的心搏停止
Adrenaline's unreliable. Went him for survive a cardiac arrest.
但急救人员到达后 第一件事
When EMT is arrive, first thing
就是给你注射一剂肾上腺素
they do is jammed you with the shot of epinephrine.
-两种混合在一起就是 -毒药
- Which is toxic when combined with. - Adrenaline.
所以 万一注射的肾上腺素杀不死他
So, any of the chance of adrenaline shot doesn't kill him.
急救人员会补上致命一针
The EMT's will.
芝加哥 伊利诺斯州
一天晚上 他丢下圣经学习小组
He left a Bible study group
去找一个年轻的信徒
for the young devotee, one night.
他们两个星期后才发现她的尸体
They wouldn't found her body until two weeks later.
验尸官说她堕过一次胎
The autopsy said she had an abortion.
她告诉朋友孩子是他的
She was telling her friends that it was his.
他花了两千两百万美元作封口费
Cost him 22 million dollars to quash it up.
好了 我们开始吧
Okay, let's get this over with.
保佑你 下一位
Bless you, next.
坐到这边来啊?
Would you come sit right here?
你是新来的吧 来了多久了
You're new here, aren't you? How long have you been here?
两星期了 先生
Two weeks, sir.
-你多大了? -18岁
- How old are you? - 18.
18岁啊
18.
不能找个美女帅哥来监视吗?
You could've found someone more attractive to spy out.
他还在吃东西
He still eating.
浓汤 沙拉 三明治 双层巧克力蛋糕
Soup, salad, sandwich... double chocolate cake.
毕肖普 我都饿了
Bishop, I'm hungry.
餐厅那家伙手上都是绷带
The guy at the delly, he had bandage on all of his fingers.
你要是在三明治里吃到绷带 那可不能怪我
If you find a bandage in your sandwich, it wouldn't be mine.
可以了
We're all clear.
感觉怎么样 沃恩?
How do you feel, Vaughn?
你觉得怎样? 弗兰克呢?
How do you think I feel? Where is Franck?
他应该马上就来了
He should be here any minute.
说曹操曹操到
Speak of the devil.
今天来点特别的 我心情不错
Give me something special today. I feel like celebrating.
我有一次心灵辅导要做
I have a spirit work to do.
-那货是个瘾君子 -他在给他注射氯胺酮
- The guy's a junkie. - He's giving him a ketamine.
氯胺酮 一种麻醉药
那又怎样
So?
氯胺酮会中和肾上腺素 那就没用了
Ketamine counteracts adrenaline. This won't work now.
上帝曾拍过我的肩膀
I have been tap on the shoulder...by God.
你准备怎么办?
What do you want to do?
国王之剑曾碰过我的肩膀
My shoulder was touched by the sword of the king.
他让我站起来
He told me to rise...
我们得收手了
We gotta pack it up.
-等等 -他可能会回来
- Wait, wait. - If he comes back in here.
戴上手套
Puts your gloves on.
是我 你好? 是的 没错
Yes, hello? Yes, yes it is.
动手
Let's go.
把这个塞进去
Put it down this right.
塞进喉咙里 让他窒息
Down his throat. He needs to choked.
如果他们觉得现在这种市场下
If they think that I'm going to pay
我会为个四居室付全价 那他们一定疯了
full price for a four bedroom in this market, they crazy.
我如何去改变世界?
How can I change the world?
我如何为了我的子民而进化自身
How can I be a better man for my creatures.
-走吧 -有时我想知道
- Let's go. - Sometimes I wonder.
有时我 那份力量 那份勇气
Sometimes I... ...the strength, the courage.
我看着镜中的自己 思考着...
I look at myself in the mirror and think...
天哪
Christ.
拉尔夫 进来
Ralph, get in here.
-怎么了? -你说呢?
- What is it? - What is it?
-他死了 -没错
- Is he dead? - Yeah.
混帐东西 我早知道会出事
Stupid motherfucker. I knew this gonna happen.
把这堆鬼东西收拾好
Get all this shit round up,
给我弄出去 越快越好
get out the fuck out of here, as fast as you can.
把他抬起来
Try and pick him up.
操
Fuck!
去看看
Go check it out.
把镜子拿下来
Take it off the wall.
墙里有人
Hey, on the wall.
跟着他
Follow him.
封锁出口 派两个人到屋顶 快点
Cover the exit and give me two guys on the roof, now.
他在那
There he is.
保持镇静
Stay calm.
我们得分头行动
They are looking for two men.
中途会有班转机
There a connecting flight out of midway.
我从奥哈拉飞回去 明天在我家碰头
I'll fly from O'Hara and meet you at house tomorrow.
这边 走吧
Right this way. Let's go.
安德鲁 沃恩
Andrew Vaughn,
极受争议的狂热宗教分子...
the controversial and polarizing religious figure...
被证实死亡
has been pronounce dead.
警方仍在调查现场发生的枪击
Police are still investigating the shooting
目前还未找到肇事者
that occur short there after the perpetrators has not been found.
五个人都死了
All five are killed.
组里也许有你认识的人
You probably knew some of the man on that team.
B终点站
Terminal B.
下一班车 在街那边 15分钟后出发
Next bus, down on the street leaves in 15 minutes.
谢谢
Thanks.
-这车什么时候开? -还有15分钟
- When does this leaves? - In 15 minutes.
那我们还有的是时间
That gives us much time then.
你要干什么?
What do you want?
我想知道你怎么还活着
I wonder what you doing alive.
上次我看见你 你脑袋上挨了颗枪子
Last time I saw you, you had a bullet in your head.
在开普敦到底发生了什么?
What really happened in Cape Town?
-其他组员呢? -都死了
- Where's the rest of your team? - They're dead.
是谁雇的你? 哈里还是迪恩
Who paid you? Was it Harry or Dean.
迪恩给了我一大笔钱 让我杀死其他人
Dean paid me a very large amount of money to kill the others.
再假造自己的死亡 从此销声匿迹
Tell me to fake my death, disappear.
你知道他还对我说了什么吗?
You know what else he told me?
哈里对一次搞砸的行动起了疑心
That Harry was getting suspicious about a blown operation.
他要告发我们 我们不能坐视不理
He's about to blow the whistle. It had to be taken care of.
你知道负责任务的人吗?
Did you know just the man for the job?
知道迪恩下落的那个人
Someone who could get Dean.
不是因为你杀了他吧
It's not the fact that you killed him, is it?
而是因为你这么容易就被耍了
It's that they played you so easily.
所以你才会不爽
That's what bothers you.
没错吧?
Am I right?
-什么事? -对你来说不太妙
- Well? - Not so good for your side.
那是我的两队精英 看来得多派点人了
Those were two my best teams. I guess I had to send more.
你就省省吧 我亲自来找你
Save the fuel. I'm coming for you.
你什么时候回家?
When are you gonna be home?
-我饿死了 -你在哪?
- I'm really hungry. - Where are you?
我在客厅里
I'm in the living room.
-坐在沙发上 -好
- Sit down on the couch. - Okay.
我猜你身边一定有人
I guess you are not alone.
左边的垫子下面有把枪
There is a gun under the left-side cushion.
已经上膛了 没开保险
It's loaded and the safety's off.
-但我不是左撇子 -那你死定了
- But I'm not a lefty. - Then you gonna die.
好吧 等你回来再说
All right, I see you when you get here.
5分钟内就到
I'll be there in five.
-谁派来的这些人? -我的雇主
- Who sent those guys? - The man who employs me.
把架子顶上的装备都拿到船上
Grab all the gear on the top shelf and put it in the boat.
胜利靠谨慎
约翰 D.E.芬奇
准备好了吗?
Are we set?
上船
Get in the boat.
你有想过你杀的人吗?
Do you ever think about the people you've killed?
没有
No.
你杀过你认识的人吗?
Have you ever killed someone you know?
杀过
Yes.
感觉有什么不一样吗?
Did it feel any different?
当时不会
Not in the moment.
之后的话...
After...
会事先警告他们吗? 给他们准备的时间?
Any kind of warning? Time to prepare?
给他们点时间...
Kind of time to ...
和解
Make peace.
不可能和解
There's no peace.
所以 最好不让他们知道你要来了
So, it's best not to let them know when you're coming.
是的
Yes.
我觉得反正也没什么区别
I guess it doesn't really matter anyway,
终究死的是他们不是你 对吧?
as long as they're dead and you not, right?
你好 芬奇
Hello, Finch.
你们是谁? 要干什么?
Who are you? What are you doing here?
你给我听清楚
You just listen to me closely.
我可是未达目的不择手段 明白吗?
I don't care who I hurt or who I killed, understand?
求求你 不要 别这样
Please, no, no, no.
把我想知道的都告诉我
You're gonna tell me exactly that I came for to find out.
迪恩在哪?
Where's Dean?
我会做出什么事就看你的表现了
It's up to you how far I go.
手指
Fingers.
手腕?
Wrist?
-还是手肘 -求你 快告诉他吧
- Elbow? - Please, just tell him what he wants to know.
好吧... 碳素广场300号
Okay, okay...300, Carbon Plaza.
碳素广场300号 我发誓他就在那
300, Carbon Plaza. That's where he is. I swear.
看来你们失去了一顿美味晚餐
It's like you going to miss a good dinner.
你个混蛋
I got you, bastard.
-喂 -哈里的命值多少钱?
- Yes. - How much was Harry's life worth?
五千万
50 million.
我可以给你承诺
And here's what I'm gonna do.
24小时内给你汇一千万 银行你选
10 million wired to a bank of your choice, within 24 hours.
-很划算 你应该接受 -不感兴趣
- It's a good deal, you should take it. - Not interested.
杀手怎么也有良心了
And killer gets a conscience.
我那么做是出于职业道德 毕肖普先生
I do that as a breach of professional ethic, Mr. Bishop.
哈里的死只是纯粹的生意
Harry's death is business. Pure and simple.
现在可没那么简单了
It's not gonna be so simple now.
你说对了 因为现在
You get that right. Cause now
我要对悬赏你 重金悬赏
I'm gonna put a price on your head. It's so big...
就连你照镜子的时候
When you look in the mirror,
镜中的倒影都会朝你开枪
your reflection are gonna shoot you in the face.
-你活不久了 -你真蠢
- You won't survive that long. - You're a fool.
你以为你会先我一步得手吗?
You think you can get to me before I get to you?
我已经来了
I already have.
会议室E
-会议室E在哪? -上一层 先生
- Where's conference room, E? - Floor upstairs, sir.
他在大楼里 快护送我出去
He's in the building. Get me the fuck out of here.
-找到毕肖普了吗? -还没有
- They find Bishop? - Nothing yet.
给我滚下车 快点 滚下去 快
Get out the fucking bus. Move, out the fucking bus. Move!
下车
Go.
倒回去 快点 快走
Move back up. Come on. Let's go.
去你的吧
Fuck you.
接下来有什么安排?
What's the plan, now?
人间蒸发
Disappear.
-起个新名字 换份工作 -一起吗?
- New names, occupation. - Together?
随你的便
That's up to you.
我们干什么去? 撒泼尿?
What we gonna do? We gonna widdle?
做个上下铺的床?
Making a bunk beds?
还是去卖厕纸?
We gonna do a TP?
喝水吗?
Want a water?
我内心总是充满了...
I've always had this...
愤怒 现在我觉得我有个...
anger inside. Now I feel like I have a...
宣泄的地方 我会想念这种感觉
a place to put it. I think I would miss this.
而现在我得罢手了
I had stop now.
我以前总是有办法招揽生意 而且...
I had got always a business for myself and...
很多人愿意付钱给我...
a lot of people out there who would pay ...
还有 我觉得你错了
And I think you were wrong.
复仇才是任务的关键
Vengeance is the mission.
加油站
燃油&食物
-要买什么吗? -不用了
- You want anything? - No.
最后机会
Last chance.
真的不用了
I'm good.
斯蒂夫
Steve.
对于发生的一切我很抱歉
Sorry for everything that happened.
你了解我 哥们 我不在乎
You know me, man. I don't give a shit.
斯蒂夫
如果你看到这个
那你就死了!
毕肖普
成功靠准备
看2号摄像头
Watch number two.